<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jadam on Greengoblin510</title>
    <link>https://greengoblin510.com/tags/Jadam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jadam on Greengoblin510</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:29:56 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://greengoblin510.com/tags/Jadam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JWA</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Shop/JWA/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:29:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Shop/JWA/</guid>
      <description>JWA - Jadam Wetting Agent      Lantern And Goblin   Jadam Wetting agent is a natural emulsifier and wetting agent that breaks down completely in 72hrs. Not using synthetic foaming and wetting agents help protect the waterways by not letting the synthetic soaps and foaming agents into those waterways. Not only the Jadam wetting agent breaks down naturally in the soil even though it’s not recommended to water indirectly but drips and drops falling of the plant from a foliar application is nothing to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JMS Jadam Microbal Solution</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/natural-Farming/JADAM/JMS/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:21:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/natural-Farming/JADAM/JMS/</guid>
      <description>How to Cultivate JMS (Jadam Microbial Solution) Charge your soil with Free Microbes.       Hey, Growmies today I&#39;m going to show you how to make JMS or jadam microbial solution. First, let&#39;s talk about why you would want to make JMS. Like buying microbes from reputable companies like recharge and plant revolution you can cultivate them on your own. what&#39;s even more dope about that is the microbes will be already adapted to your environment and won’t have a population fall off over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JS Jadam Sulfur</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/natural-Farming/JADAM/JS/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:21:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/natural-Farming/JADAM/JS/</guid>
      <description>How To Make Jadam Sulfur For Pest And Disease Control       Today I show you how to make Jadam Sulfur for pest and disease control.❇Some Things you&amp;rsquo;ll need are:
➡Sodium Hydroxide (aka Lye) - https://amzn.to/3haMjwz
➡Sulfur - https://amzn.to/3h7fnFs
➡A wooden Stir stick
➡Heat Resistant Bucket
➡Scale
➡Water and Things To measure water.
 Measurement Chart    To Learn More
Jadam Organic Farming - https://amzn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
