<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greengoblin510</title>
    <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Greengoblin510</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alfalfa - Kelp of The Land</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/AlfalfaTheLandKelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/AlfalfaTheLandKelp/</guid>
      <description>Alfalfa is another one of natures gifts providing for animals and people. Alfalfa is also called Lucerne in most places outside of north America and is cultivated for a multitude of uses from grazing animal feed, hay, mulch, cover crop and green manure. Alfalfa is a perennial that closely resembles clover until the plant is more mature. It grows 1 - 3 feet tall and is native to warmer temperate climates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aloe Vera - The Swiss Army Knife In the Garden</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/AloeVera-SwissArmyKnifeInTheGarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/AloeVera-SwissArmyKnifeInTheGarden/</guid>
      <description>Aloe   What is Aloe Vera Made Of     Aloe vera has many medicinal properties. Scientists have discovered Nearly 200 chemical Compounds in Aloe vera. Much like our beloved cannabis plant the constituents of Aloe work to together like the entourage effect. They all work together to create health giving benefits to both humans and plants. The main active chemical constituents of Aloe vera are: amino acids, anthraquinones, enzymes, minerals, vitamins, lignins, monosaccharide, polysaccharides, salicylic acid, saponins, and sterols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insect Frass - The waste Diverter</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Insect-frass-The-waste-diverter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Insect-frass-The-waste-diverter/</guid>
      <description>Insect Frass is much like worm castings and can provide a ton of benefits for soil building and plant growth. The main difference in insect frass is that the castings aka poop or undigestible food is from insects mostly crickets, mealworms, or black soldier flies. Insect Frass can help provide nutrients and protection to our crops by its unique make up and worms love it as a feed stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelp - The Oceans Filter</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Kelp-TheOceansFilter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Kelp-TheOceansFilter/</guid>
      <description>What Is Kelp      Kelp   Interesting fact about kelp is that is isn&amp;rsquo;t a plant at all its actually a multicellular organism know as a heterokont making it adsorb nutrients in a very different way compared to plants. Kelp adsorbs nutrients much like fungi do by direct adsorption!
 Kelp is a wonderful dynamic accumulator of nutrients. It accomplishes this by attaching its self to the ocean floor usually on something heavy like a rock via the holdfast(A root like structure).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neem The Tree That solves Global Problems</title>
      <link>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Neem-The-Village-Phamacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:19:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greengoblin510.com/Amendment-Of-The-Week/posts/Neem-The-Village-Phamacy/</guid>
      <description>Neem&amp;rsquo;s Origin:      Neem   Neem is another one of natures gifts that is mainly cultivated in the subcontinente of India. Neem is a member of mahogany family Meliaceae. Its Also know as the botanical name Azadriachta indica
Neem has been used for thousands of years by humans for a multitude of things including
 Skin Conditions like zits, eczema, psoriasis. mouth care with teeth cleanings and mouth wash&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
